- Is that for me? - No!
- هل هذا لي؟ - لا!
Thanks anyways, but it would be a waste.
شكراً على كل حال، لكن ذلك سيكون مضيعة للوقت.
I like a different kind of sweet now.
أحب الآن نوعاً مختلفاً من الحلويات.
What?
ماذا؟
Your lips.
شفتيكِ.
You use a different car every time!
تستخدم سيارة مختلفة في كل مرة!
I'm actually even willing to give you my entire house.
بل إنني على استعداد حتى لمنحك منزلي بأكمله.
Just make sure you won't marry Yuri.
تأكد فقط من أنك لن تتزوج يوري.
Cause remember,
تذكر،
you're mine.
أنت ملكي.
Hi, Jay!
مرحباً يا جاي!
We found out that your father is the son of uh...
اكتشفنا أن والدك هو ابن...
business tycoon?
قطب أعمال؟
Why are they together?
لماذا هما معاً؟
I'm confused, too.
أنا أيضاً أشعر بالحيرة.
We’ll figure it out.
سنجد حلاً.
Hey, dad.
مرحباً يا أبي.
I'll teach you some Japanese words.
سأعلمك بعض الكلمات اليابانية.
Say...
يقول...
[in Japanese] I love you.
[باللغة اليابانية] أحبك.
Can I kiss you again?
هل يمكنني تقبيلك مرة أخرى؟
Why are you doing this to me, Jay?
لماذا تفعل هذا بي يا جاي؟
Tell me and I'll leave you alone!
أخبرني وسأتركك وشأنك!
Fine!
بخير!
I'm not sure about what I feel,
لست متأكداً مما أشعر به،
but this is what's right, it should be Yuri!
لكن هذا هو الصواب، يجب أن يكون يوري!
Because of that fucking engagement?
بسبب تلك الخطوبة اللعينة؟
No.
لا.
Not me.
ليس أنا.
I love you, Jay.
أحبك يا جاي.
I love you too, Keifer.
أحبك أيضاً يا كيفر.
[Ci-N snoring]
[شخير سي-إن]
I love you, Jay.
أحبك يا جاي.
I love you too, Keifer.
أحبك أيضاً يا كيفر.
Oh sh-
يا إلهي-
You idiot, you scared me.
أيها الأحمق، لقد أرعبتني.
Hello?
مرحبًا؟
How are you?
كيف حالك؟
I got scolded because I went home late.
تم توبيخي لأنني عدت إلى المنزل متأخراً.
What if we just tell them?
ماذا لو أخبرناهم بذلك؟
Tell them what?
أخبرهم ماذا؟
That you're pregnant and we'll get married.
أنكِ حامل وسنتزوج.
Shut up.
اسكت.
You're crazy.
أنت مجنون.
Let's go to sleep.
هيا بنا ننام.
Okay, you go ahead.
حسناً، تفضل.
I still have something else to do.
لا يزال لدي شيء آخر لأفعله.
I've got to go.
يجب أن أذهب.
You might end up having wet dreams about me.
قد ينتهي بك الأمر إلى أن تحلم بي أحلاماً رطبة.
Wow, bold of you to say.
يا له من كلام جريء منك!
Well then,
حسناً إذاً،
good night,
طاب مساؤك،
my life.
حياتي.
Good night.
طاب مساؤك.
I love you.
أحبك.
To infinity,
إلى ما لا نهاية،
and beyond.
وما وراء ذلك.
I...
أنا...
I love...
أحب...
myself!
نفسي!
Who's that?
من هو الذي؟
What?
ماذا؟
Where? Do you see someone?
أين؟ هل ترى أحداً؟
Go on, keep playing dumb.
استمر في التظاهر بالغباء.
I'll tell Keifer that you have a boyfriend!
سأخبر كيفر أن لديكِ حبيباً!
What boyfriend are you talking about?
عن أي حبيب تتحدثين؟
Go on, tell everybody!
هيا، أخبر الجميع!
Huh?
هاه؟
So who is that? Let me see.
إذن من هذا؟ دعني أرى.
Nothing, huh? "I love you!"
لا شيء، أليس كذلك؟ "أحبك!"
So what?
وماذا في ذلك؟
Let's just go to sleep.
هيا بنا ننام.
- Why won't you show it to me? - Because I don't want to!
- لماذا لا تريني إياه؟ - لأنني لا أريد ذلك!
Let me see, Jay.
دعني أرى يا جاي.
Wow, it's like you'll die if you won't find out.
يا للعجب، يبدو الأمر وكأنك ستموت إن لم تكتشف ذلك.
Just let me see it.
دعني أراه فقط.
Give it to me.
أعطني إياه.
- I'll bite you! - Just one peek, Jay!
- سأعضك! - مجرد نظرة خاطفة يا جاي!
- Gross, let me see! - Why, did you tell me
- مقرف، دعني أرى! - لماذا، هل أخبرتني؟
what you talked about with Rakki?
ما الذي تحدثت عنه مع راكي؟
[ARIES] Hey! If you don't want to sleep, let others sleep.
[برج الحمل] مهلاً! إذا كنت لا تريد النوم، دع الآخرين ينامون.
There you go, loudmouth!
ها قد انتهيت، أيها الثرثار!
Why me?
لماذا أنا؟
Go back to your bed.
عد إلى سريرك.
- Okay fine. - Go to sleep.
- حسناً، لا بأس. - اذهب للنوم.
Wow!
رائع!
- You’re so noisy! - You're treating me like this now?
- أنت مزعج للغاية! - هل تعاملني هكذا الآن؟
I won’t forget this!
لن أنسى هذا!
Just go to sleep.
اذهب للنوم.
- Go on, throw that pillow. - Whatever, this is mine now!
- هيا، ارمِ تلك الوسادة. - حسناً، هذه ملكي الآن!
You don't have a pillow anymore.
لم يعد لديك وسادة.
- Give it back! - No!
- أعده! - لا!
Okay, whatever.
حسناً، لا يهم.
What!?
ماذا!؟
Can I borrow?
هل يمكنني الاستعارة؟
I'm so sleepy.
أشعر بنعاس شديد.
Me too.
أنا أيضاً.
This is your fault!
هذا خطأك!
You were so annoying last night,
لقد كنت مزعجاً للغاية الليلة الماضية،
you wouldn't let me sleep.
لم تدعني أنام.
If you had just told me who that "I love you" was for,
لو كنتَ أخبرتني فقط لمن كانت عبارة "أحبك" موجهة،
we could've fallen asleep properly.
كان بإمكاننا أن ننام بشكل صحيح.
Quiet!
هادئ!
You're so annoying, that's why I don't want to tell you.
أنت مزعج للغاية، ولهذا السبب لا أريد أن أخبرك.
I'll tell Keifer on you.
سأخبر كيفر عنك.
Go ahead, tell him!
هيا، أخبره!
What happened to your eyes?
ماذا حدث لعينيك؟
It's his fault.
إنه خطأه.
My fault? You're the reason I woke up!
خطئي؟ أنت السبب في استيقاظي!
As if!
كأنني سأفعل!
- It's your fault! - No, it's yours!
- هذا خطؤك! - لا، بل خطؤك أنت!
You're so noisy!
أنت مزعج للغاية!
Enough.
كافٍ.
Stop bickering.
توقفوا عن الشجار.
You sound so dumb.
كلامك يبدو غبياً جداً.
Boys.
يا أولاد.
You brought food!
لقد أحضرت طعاماً!
Oh, hey hey!
أوه، هي هي!
Yay!
ياي!
Wait, calm down.
انتظر، اهدأ.
Whatever.
أيا كان.
This is mine.
هذا ملكي.
I'm not yet ready to face Yuri.
لستُ مستعداً بعد لمواجهة يوري.
I feel awkward around him.
أشعر بالحرج في وجوده.
I don't want to hurt him,
لا أريد أن أؤذيه،
but I also don't want to give him false hope.
لكنني أيضاً لا أريد أن أعطيه أملاً كاذباً.
I don't know anymore.
لم أعد أعرف.
Why isn't the King of Assholes here yet?
لماذا لم يأتِ ملك الأوغاد بعد؟
I don't know if it would be easier to tell Yuri the truth
لا أعرف ما إذا كان من الأسهل إخبار يوري بالحقيقة
if he were here.
لو كان هنا.
Thank you guys.
شكراً لكم جميعاً.
He won't come in.
لن يدخل.
Huh?
هاه؟
Keifer's not going to school today
كيفر لن يذهب إلى المدرسة اليوم
if he's the one you're looking for.
إذا كان هو الشخص الذي تبحث عنه.
His dad went home, and he's dealing with a lot.
عاد والده إلى المنزل، وهو يواجه الكثير من الأمور.
Huh, what do I care about him?
هاه، ما الذي يهمني بشأنه؟
Besides, Keifer isn't the one I'm looking for.
إضافة إلى ذلك، كيفر ليس الشخص الذي أبحث عنه.
So annoying,
مزعج للغاية،
is it that obvious that I'm looking for him?
هل من الواضح أنني أبحث عنه؟
Hey.
يا.
Why are you so quiet?
لماذا أنت صامتٌ هكذا؟
Huh?
هاه؟
She's definitely spaced out.
إنها بالتأكيد شاردة الذهن.
Maybe she just misses someone.
ربما هي فقط تفتقد شخصاً ما.
Or maybe it's not Keifer she's missing.
أو ربما ليس كيفر هو من تفتقده.
Who?
من؟
Maybe the one she was saying "I love-"
ربما كانت تقول "أنا أحب-"
Hey! Shut your mouth!
يا! أغلق فمك!
Why are you defensive?
لماذا تتخذ موقفاً دفاعياً؟
Whatever!
أيا كان!
Why won't you say it?
لماذا لا تقول ذلك؟
You want to know what Jay-jay did last night?
هل تريد أن تعرف ماذا فعل جاي جاي الليلة الماضية؟
It was bad. You want to know?
كان الأمر سيئاً. هل تريد أن تعرف؟
Don't you dare.
إياك أن تفعل.
Meow!
مواء!
Who's that?
من هو الذي؟
Edy!
إيدي!
You're dead!
أنت ميت!
Hey! That cat's name is not Edy!
مهلاً! اسم تلك القطة ليس إيدي!
Good thing Edy saved me.
لحسن الحظ أن إيدي أنقذني.
Give me some.
أعطني بعضاً.
[background chattering]
[ثرثرة في الخلفية]
Hey, give me some of that too!
هيا، أعطني بعضاً من ذلك أيضاً!
Fuck you, you're so stingy!
تباً لك، أنت بخيل جداً!
Hey! Me too!
مرحباً! أنا أيضاً!
No, Edy.
حسناً يا إيدي.
Stop.
قف.
No, Edy!
حسناً يا إيدي!
Stop!
قف!
Hey!
يا!
No!
لا!
He hasn't been coming to school for days, is he okay?
لم يأتِ إلى المدرسة منذ أيام، هل هو بخير؟
Meow!
مواء!
Edy.
إيدي.
What happened to this guy?
ماذا حدث لهذا الرجل؟
Meow!
مواء!
Now I can’t sleep even more.
الآن لا أستطيع النوم أكثر من أي وقت مضى.
I'm so annoyed.
أنا منزعج للغاية.
After saying "I love you" the other day,
بعد أن قلت "أحبك" في اليوم الآخر،
he suddenly disappeared.
اختفى فجأة.
No updates at all.
لا توجد أي تحديثات على الإطلاق.
[phone buzzing]
[رنين الهاتف]
I miss you.
أفتقدك.
What happened?
ماذا حدث؟
Why did it take you so long to call?
لماذا استغرق الأمر كل هذا الوقت للاتصال؟
Long story.
قصة طويلة.
How are you?
كيف حالك؟
Is Yuri making moves while I'm gone?
هل يقوم يوري بحركاتٍ ما أثناء غيابي؟
Stupid.
غبي.
I was worried about you.
كنت قلقاً عليك.
You didn't message me for days,
لم تراسلني منذ أيام،
and that's what you're worried about?
وهذا ما يقلقك ؟
I told you.
أخبرتك.
I have a lot on my plate right now.
لدي الكثير من الأمور التي تشغلني حالياً.
And…
و…
I'm not sure when I'll be able to come back.
لست متأكدًا متى سأتمكن من العودة.
Really?
حقًا؟
What is it about?
ما هو موضوعه؟
You couldn't even send one text, one update?
ألم تستطع حتى إرسال رسالة نصية واحدة، أو تحديث واحد؟
You need me to update you so bad?
هل تحتاجني بشدة لأطلعك على آخر المستجدات؟
No.
لا.
I just want to know how big that problem is
أريد فقط أن أعرف مدى ضخامة هذه المشكلة
that you can't even send a message.
أنك لا تستطيع حتى إرسال رسالة.
Just…
فقط…
family problems.
مشاكل عائلية.
Can't even send a text?
لا يمكنك حتى إرسال رسالة نصية؟
Hey.
يا.
What happened to you?
ما حدث لك؟
You're kind of cute when you're like that.
أنتِ لطيفة نوعاً ما عندما تكونين هكذا.
I like it.
أحبها.
I wish I could see your face right now.
أتمنى لو أستطيع رؤية وجهك الآن.
I can send a picture if you want?
هل تريد أن أرسل لك صورة؟
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
Nude photo, please.
صورة عارية، من فضلك.
Maybe I should just stop talking to you forever.
ربما يجب أن أتوقف عن التحدث إليك إلى الأبد.
Just kidding.
أنا فقط أمزح.
But seriously, Keifer.
لكن بجدية يا كيفر.
What's going on?
ماذا يحدث هنا؟
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
3 days ago
قبل 3 أيام
Girls.
فتيات.
What happened?
ماذا حدث؟
It's because of Sir…
ذلك بفضل السيد...
Did you get hurt?
هل تعرضت لأذى؟
We're okay.
نحن بخير.
How about the kids?
وماذا عن الأطفال؟
They're alright.
هم بخير.
Alright then, we need to clean up the mess immediately.
حسنًا، علينا تنظيف الفوضى فورًا.
Did that man come here?
هل أتى ذلك الرجل إلى هنا؟
Sir.
سيد.
Where's Keiren?
أين كيرين؟
- Go on, clean up. - Keiren!
- هيا، نظف المكان. - كيرين!
Keifer.
كيفر.
Sir, excuse me.
سيدي، معذرةً.
It's okay.
لا بأس.
I'm here now.
أنا هنا الآن.
Where did you go?
أين ذهبت؟
You know dad already went back to the country.
أنت تعلم أن أبي قد عاد بالفعل إلى البلاد.
But you still chose to leave.
لكنك مع ذلك اخترت الرحيل.
Good thing he didn't take us.
من حسن الحظ أنه لم يأخذنا معه.
I don't want to go with him.
لا أريد الذهاب معه.
He won't be able to take you away from us
لن يستطيع أن يأخذك بعيدًا عنا
as long as we're here.
طالما نحن هنا.
So what's your plan now?
إذن ما هي خطتك الآن؟
I'm almost of legal age.
أنا على وشك بلوغ السن القانونية.
I will fight for your custody.
سأقاتل من أجل حضانتك.
So we'll just wait for your birthday?
إذن سننتظر حتى عيد ميلادك؟
Is that it?
هل هذا كل شيء؟
What if they take Keiren before that happens?
ماذا لو أخذوا كيرين قبل حدوث ذلك؟
No.
لا.
That will never happen.
هذا لن يحدث أبداً.
Okay?
تمام؟
I hope you really mean what you're saying.
أتمنى أن تكون جاداً فيما تقوله.
Come on. Let's go to sleep.
هيا بنا. لنذهب إلى النوم.
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
You rest now.
استرح الآن.
Hello?
مرحبًا؟
Good evening, Mr. Ryder.
مساء الخير يا سيد رايدر.
I'm sorry to disturb.
أعتذر عن الإزعاج.
I just need to talk to you about something.
أريد فقط أن أتحدث معك بشأن أمر ما.
Is this about your legal rights?
هل يتعلق الأمر بحقوقك القانونية؟
Yes.
نعم.
I fear that this is what I dreaded since mom's death.
أخشى أن يكون هذا هو ما كنت أخشاه منذ وفاة أمي.
It's finally beginning.
لقد بدأت أخيراً.
I guess he’s back again.
أظن أنه عاد مجدداً.
Don’t worry, I'll prepare the necessary paperwork
لا تقلق، سأقوم بإعداد الأوراق اللازمة
and update you once everything is ready.
وسأبلغكم بالتحديثات حالما يصبح كل شيء جاهزاً.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Come on, you're so slow.
هيا، أنت بطيء جداً.
At least, it's not that hot.
على الأقل، ليس الجو حاراً جداً.
What do you mean "not hot"? I'm already drenched in sweat.
ماذا تقصد بـ "ليس ساخناً"؟ أنا غارق في العرق بالفعل.
- It's because you don't shower! - Yuck.
- السبب هو أنك لا تستحم! - مقرف.
Oh, is this your ride?
أوه، هل هذه سيارتك؟
- Nice timing, it's really hot today. - That's not my ride.
- توقيت مناسب، الجو حار جداً اليوم. - هذه ليست سيارتي.
Oh, they're in uniform.
أوه، إنهم يرتدون الزي الرسمي.
Are you Jasper Jean Mariano?
هل أنت جاسبر جان ماريانو؟
Ci-N Peralta and Michael Aries Fernandez?
سي-إن بيرالتا ومايكل أريس فرنانديز؟
Uh yes, that's us. Why?
أجل، هذا نحن. لماذا؟
Aries!
بُرْجُ الحَمَل!
That's Ella.
هذه إيلا.
The Watson Family is asking for you.
عائلة واتسون تطلبك.
Watson Family?
عائلة واتسون؟
Is this Keifer's doing?
هل هذا من فعل كيفر؟
We were strictly told not to give any information.
لقد طُلب منا بشدة عدم إعطاء أي معلومات.
Jay, this isn't Keifer's doing.
جاي، هذا ليس من فعل كيفر.
This might be his dad.
قد يكون هذا والده.
Let's not get in, we should leave.
دعونا لا ندخل، يجب أن نغادر.
Just get in.
ادخل فقط.
No.
لا.
- He says get in. - Jay!
- يقول ادخل. - جاي!
Come on, let's go.
هيا بنا، لنذهب.
Hey, careful!
انتبه!
- Ouch! - Why did you get in?
- آخ! - لماذا دخلت؟
Damn, it'so hot in here.
يا إلهي، الجو حار جداً هنا.
This is really my house.
هذا بيتي حقاً.
You're broke!
أنت مفلس!
What, am I not allowed to dream?
ماذا، ألا يحق لي أن أحلم؟
Another black van?
شاحنة سوداء أخرى؟
I wonder who this is.
أتساءل من يكون هذا.
Oh, they're here.
أوه، لقد وصلوا.
- Ouch. - It's Ci-N.
- آخ. - إنه سي-إن.
It's actually bigger in person.
إنها في الواقع أكبر حجماً على أرض الواقع.
Why? Where did you see this before?
لماذا؟ أين رأيت هذا من قبل؟
In a picture.
في صورة.
Wait,
انتظر،
why are we here anyways?
لماذا نحن هنا على أي حال؟
I don't know.
لا أعرف.
Wait, where's Keifer?
لحظة، أين كيفر؟
That's Keifer's dad.
هذا والد كيفر.
That's his dad?
هذا والده؟
Good morning.
صباح الخير.
Are we all complete?
هل نحن جميعاً كاملون؟
Why are we here?
لماذا نحن هنا؟
Is Keifer here too?
هل كيفر موجود هنا أيضاً؟
Mr. Watson.
السيد واتسون.
Why are we here?
لماذا نحن هنا؟
Aries Fernandez.
آريس فرنانديز.
You still haven't changed.
ما زلت لم تتغير.
Still impatient.
ما زلتُ متلهفاً.
Why?
لماذا؟
Am I not allowed to have lunch with my son's friends?
هل يُمنع عليّ تناول الغداء مع أصدقاء ابني؟
Welcome to my home, guys.
أهلاً بكم في منزلي يا رفاق.
They even arrived together. I can't focus.
حتى أنهم وصلوا معاً. لا أستطيع التركيز.
But since they came together, I guess they're okay now?
لكن بما أنهم اجتمعوا معاً، أعتقد أنهم بخير الآن؟
I hope they're both okay.
أتمنى أن يكون كلاهما بخير.
Even if it feels like I'm the one who won't be okay seeing them together.
حتى لو شعرتُ بأنني الشخص الوحيد الذي لن يكون على ما يرام برؤيتهما معًا.
Why did your dad bring us here?
لماذا أحضرنا والدك إلى هنا؟
Psst!
همس!
What's going on?
ماذا يحدث هنا؟
Why?
لماذا؟
Why is it just us?
لماذا نحن فقط؟
Good thing no one else followed.
من حسن الحظ أن أحداً آخر لم يتبعه.
Jay.
جاي.
Wait.
انتظر.
What is this?
ما هذا؟
What's happening?
ماذا يحدث؟
Did you get here earlier?
هل وصلت إلى هنا مبكراً؟
We need your cooperation.
نحن بحاجة إلى تعاونكم.
Dad is up to something.
أبي يخطط لشيء ما.
He wouldn't bring us here without a reason.
لن يحضرنا إلى هنا بدون سبب.
We don't know what it is.
لا نعرف ما هو.
But one thing's for sure,
لكن هناك شيء واحد مؤكد،
Keiren is his target.
كيرين هو هدفه.
He can use us anytime, Jay.
بإمكانه الاستعانة بنا في أي وقت يا جاي.
Wait.
انتظر.
I don't understand anything.
لا أفهم شيئاً.
What do you mean "kidnapped"?
ماذا تقصد بكلمة "اختطاف"؟
You were kidnapped?
هل تم اختطافك؟
Well, he already kidnapped Keigan before.
حسناً، لقد اختطف كيغان من قبل.
So if something bad happens today,
لذا إذا حدث شيء سيء اليوم،
he'd go for Keiren.
سيذهب إلى كيرين.
Yeah.
نعم.
Good thing he didn't take our phones yet.
لحسن الحظ أنه لم يأخذ هواتفنا بعد.
We were able to roam around the house,
استطعنا التجول في أرجاء المنزل،
and I managed to contact Keifer.
وتمكنت من الاتصال بكيفر.
But I do know,
لكنني أعرف،
that if dad doesn't get what he wants,
أنه إذا لم يحصل أبي على ما يريد،
he'll do whatever it takes.
سيفعل كل ما يلزم.
I'm begging you, Jay.
أتوسل إليك يا جاي.
If something happens,
إذا حدث شيء ما،
get Keiren out of here.
أخرجوا كيرين من هنا.
Keigan will bring you guys both to safety.
سيأخذكم كيغان إلى بر الأمان.
Okay?
تمام؟
I'm scared.
أنا خائف.
What do you mean "if something happens?”
ماذا تقصد بـ "إذا حدث شيء ما"؟
I'll leave you? Is something bad going to happen?
هل سأتركك؟ هل سيحدث شيء سيء؟
Jay, don't worry about your friends.
جاي، لا تقلق بشأن أصدقائك.
They'll be safe.
سيكونون بأمان.
But I can't make that same promise to Keifer.
لكن لا يمكنني أن أقطع نفس الوعد لكيفير.
What do you mean?
ماذا تقصد؟
- Keifer? - Please, Jay. Just do what I say.
- كيفر؟ - أرجوك يا جاي. فقط افعل ما أقوله.
Okay?
تمام؟
Don't think about anything else.
لا تفكر في أي شيء آخر.
Do this for Keiren.
افعل هذا من أجل كيرين.
Do this for me.
افعل هذا من أجلي.
Okay.
تمام.
I'll do it.
سأفعل ذلك.
Good.
جيد.
Keigan, you know what to do.
كيغان، أنت تعرف ما يجب فعله.
Let's go back before we get noticed.
لنعد إلى الوراء قبل أن يلاحظنا أحد.
Come on.
تعال.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Keifer?
كيفر؟
I fucking miss you.
أفتقدك بشدة.
I know I've been busy lately, but…
أعلم أنني كنت مشغولاً مؤخراً، لكن...
I promise
أعدك
I'll make it up to you.
سأعوضك عن ذلك.
Please say something.
أرجوك قل شيئاً.
Keifer.
كيفر.
Thank you for being here.
شكراً لحضوركم.
Before you go.
قبل أن تذهب.
Shot!
طلقة!
Making yourself at home, huh?
تشعر وكأنك في بيتك، أليس كذلك؟
Where have you been, Jay?
أين كنت يا جاي؟
Just somewhere.
في مكان ما.
So, are you going to tell him,
إذن، هل ستخبره؟
or should I tell Keifer that you already have a boyfriend?
أم هل يجب أن أخبر كيفر أن لديكِ حبيباً بالفعل؟
So should I tell him?
هل يجب أن أخبره بذلك؟
Don't bother.
لا داعي للعناء.
What are you talking about?
عن ماذا تتحدث؟
Oh, nothing.
لا شيء.
- He's just hungry. - There's dessert!
- إنه جائع فقط. - هناك حلوى!
That's what I like.
هذا ما يعجبني.
Give me some.
أعطني بعضاً.
Bro, can you give me some.
يا أخي، هل يمكنك أن تعطيني بعضاً؟
Shh! Be quiet.
اصمت!
So, Keifer,
إذن، كيفر،
are you studying well?
هل تدرس جيداً؟
It's none of your business.
هذا ليس من شأنك.
I still have obligations toward you and your siblings.
لا تزال لدي التزامات تجاهك أنت وإخوتك.
Bullshit!
هراء!
Watch your language.
انتبه لكلامك.
You're in my house.
أنت في منزلي.
You used to come here to pick Keifer up.
كنت تأتي إلى هنا لاصطحاب كيفر.
Too bad, you're incomplete now.
يا للأسف، أنت الآن غير مكتمل.
Ella.
هي.
Back then, you were with my son.
في ذلك الوقت، كنت مع ابني.
Now, things seem different.
الآن، تبدو الأمور مختلفة.
You.
أنت.
What's your name?
ما اسمك؟
Uh, Jasper Jean Mariano, Sir.
أه، جاسبر جان ماريانو، سيدي.
You can call me Jay-jay.
يمكنك مناداتي جاي جاي.
Mariano…
ماريانو…
I think I have a business partner named Mariano.
أعتقد أن لدي شريكاً تجارياً اسمه ماريانو.
Who are your parents?
من هما والداك؟
Hey, jackass.
يا أحمق.
They're none of your business.
إنها ليست من شأنك.
I'm just asking her parents' names.
أنا فقط أسأل عن اسمي والديها.
There's nothing wrong with that, is there?
لا يوجد خطأ في ذلك، أليس كذلك؟
My father is Jasfher Mariano.
والدي هو جاسفير ماريانو.
My mother is Jeana Fernandez.
والدتي هي جينا فرنانديز.
The world really is small, huh?
العالم صغير حقاً، أليس كذلك؟
They have a child?
هل لديهم طفل؟
You know, your father sounds familiar to me.
أتعرف، اسم والدك يبدو مألوفاً لي.
He's a stockholder in our telecom company, your mother too.
هو مساهم في شركة الاتصالات الخاصة بنا، ووالدتك أيضاً.
She's the sister of…
هي أخت...
what's her name?
ما هو اسمها؟
Gemma? Gemma Fernandez, right?
جيما؟ جيما فرنانديز، صحيح؟
Yes.
نعم.
Okay.
تمام.
So you two are cousins, right?
إذن أنتما أبناء عمومة، صحيح؟
Wait, they had a child?
لحظة، هل أنجبا طفلاً؟
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
No offense meant.
لا أقصد الإساءة.
Because
لأن
your mom is kind of tactless, isn't she?
والدتك تفتقر إلى اللباقة نوعاً ما، أليس كذلك؟
Oh my God, did you just invite them over to insult?
يا إلهي، هل دعوتهم للتو ليشتموك؟
Why are you so affected?
لماذا أنت متأثر إلى هذا الحد؟
Just relax.
استرخِ فقط.
What do you need from all of us?
ماذا تحتاجون منا جميعاً؟
We still have classes.
لا تزال لدينا دروس.
I'm glad you mentioned that.
أنا سعيد لأنك ذكرت ذلك.
Bring me the papers.
أحضر لي الأوراق.
Sign them.
وقّع عليها.
If you don't sign it,
إذا لم توقع عليه،
I'll take full custody of Keiren.
سأتولى الحضانة الكاملة لكيرين.
Or…
أو…
give me your inheritance instead.
أعطني ميراثك بدلاً من ذلك.
That's my mom's money!
هذا مال أمي!
She worked hard for it, and she gave it to me!
لقد عملت بجد من أجله، وأعطته لي!
She doesn't have money!
إنها لا تملك المال!
She stole that from the company, from me to be exact!
لقد سرقت ذلك من الشركة، مني أنا تحديداً!
I won't sign anything!
لن أوقع على أي شيء!
If that's what you want.
إذا كان هذا ما تريده.
Keiren, run!
كيرين، اهرب!
Enough!
كافٍ!
Get down!
انزل!
Get them all out!
أخرجوهم جميعاً!
Get out!
اخرج!
Hurry up!
أسرع!
Stand up!
الوقوف!
Get out, hurry!
اخرج، أسرع!
Hurry up!
أسرع!
Where's my son?
أين ابني؟
Huh?!
هاه؟!
Did it really have to come to this?
هل كان لا بد أن يصل الأمر إلى هذا الحد؟
Bring out my son!
أخرجوا ابني!
This girl right here.
هذه الفتاة بالذات.
Jay!
جاي!
She knows where Keiren is.
إنها تعرف مكان كيرين.
Yes, drinking coffee in my pocket!
نعم، أشرب القهوة في جيبي!
In your pocket?
في جيبك؟
Drinking coffee?
هل تشرب القهوة؟
I know what kind of woman you are.
أعرف أي نوع من النساء أنتِ.
You're just after my son's money.
أنت تطمع فقط في أموال ابني.
And you…
وأنت…
you really take after your mother.
أنت تشبه والدتك كثيراً.
You're so stubborn.
أنت عنيد جداً.
You son of a bitch!
يا ابن العاهرة!
Watch your language.
انتبه لكلامك.
You're in my place.
أنت مكاني.
You won't bring my son out?
ألن تخرج ابني؟
Everyone, kneel!
الجميع، اركعوا!
Get down on your knees!
انزل على ركبتيك!
You think you're brave?
أتظن نفسك شجاعاً؟
Bring him here.
أحضروه إلى هنا.
Beat him up.
اضربه ضرباً مبرحاً.
Keifer!
كيفر!
Stop it! Have mercy.
توقف عن ذلك! ارحمنا.
Mercy?
رحمة؟
That word doesn't exist in my son's vocabulary.
هذه الكلمة غير موجودة في قاموس ابني.
He needs to be taught a lesson.
يجب تلقينه درساً.
You're all so brave, huh?
أنتم جميعاً شجعان جداً، أليس كذلك؟
So stubborn!
عنيد جداً!
You think you're tough, huh?
أتظن نفسك قوياً، أليس كذلك؟
You know what I need, don't you?
أنت تعرف ما أحتاجه، أليس كذلك؟
The papers.
الأوراق.
You!
أنت!
Sign this!
وقّع هنا!
Keifer, don't!
كيفر، لا تفعل!
Keifer!
كيفر!
Don't.
لا.
Go on, pull that trigger.
هيا، اضغط على الزناد.
Go ahead.
تفضل.
Pull it.
اسحبه.
Jay, shut up!
جاي، اصمت!
Do it.
افعلها.
Jay, what are you doing?!
جاي، ماذا تفعل؟!
Pull it already.
اسحبها الآن.
You can't do it, can you?
لا يمكنك فعل ذلك، أليس كذلك؟
What do you think people will say
ما رأيك فيما سيقوله الناس؟
when they find out a student died because of a Watson?
عندما يكتشفون أن طالباً مات بسبب واتسون؟
Wouldn't that ruin your name?
ألن يؤدي ذلك إلى تشويه سمعتك؟
Can you really kill a defenseless student?
هل يمكنك حقاً قتل طالب أعزل؟
What will your business partners say?
ماذا سيقول شركاؤك في العمل؟
What will all those people say
ماذا سيقول كل هؤلاء الناس؟
and what will my dad say?
وماذا سيقول أبي؟
You're something else.
أنت شيء آخر.
You're brave.
أنت شجاع.
Put the gun down.
ضع السلاح أرضاً.
Looks like I underestimated all of you.
يبدو أنني قللت من شأنكم جميعاً.
Well, class is adjourned.
حسناً، انتهى الدرس.
I'll see you all next time.
أراكم جميعاً في المرة القادمة.
Let's go boys.
هيا يا شباب.
Jay!
جاي!
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
Good Lord.
يا إلهي.
I thought I was going to die.
ظننت أنني سأموت.
You were really brave earlier, Jay.
لقد كنت شجاعاً حقاً في وقت سابق يا جاي.
I'm proud of you.
أنا فخور بك.
Really?
حقًا؟
Are you out of your mind?
هل فقدت عقلك؟
Do you know who you challenged?
هل تعرف من تحديته؟
That's Dylan!
هذا ديلان!
He’s a professional hitman!
إنه قاتل محترف!
Where's Keiren?
أين كيرين؟
Keiren!
كيرين!
Keifer!
كيفر!
What are we still doing here? Let's just leave.
ما الذي نفعله هنا حتى الآن؟ فلنرحل.
Don't ever do that again.
لا تفعل ذلك مرة أخرى أبداً.
You just gave him a new idea on what to do next!
لقد أعطيته للتو فكرة جديدة عما يجب فعله بعد ذلك!
Next time, think before taking some random action!
في المرة القادمة، فكر جيداً قبل اتخاذ أي إجراء عشوائي!
Just let Keifer be.
دعوا كيفر وشأنه.
He's just worried about you, okay?
هو قلق عليكِ فقط، حسناً؟
Felix, are you alright?
فيليكس، هل أنت بخير؟
It's okay, Jay.
لا بأس يا جاي.
What a stressful day.
يا له من يوم مرهق!
Oh wow, you're texting me nonstop now?
يا إلهي، هل تراسلني باستمرار الآن؟
You were so mean earlier.
لقد كنتَ لئيماً جداً في وقت سابق.
Here.
هنا.
Look at this.
انظر إلى هذا.
This place looks cheap and nice to live in.
يبدو هذا المكان رخيصاً وجميلاً للعيش فيه.
Check out this condo, Ci-N.
ألقِ نظرة على هذه الشقة، سي-إن.
- Right? - Doesn't really suit my taste.
- صحيح؟ - لا يناسب ذوقي حقاً.
Whatever. You really are the King of Assholes.
مهما يكن. أنت حقاً ملك الحمقى.
You're not going to answer that?
ألن تجيب على ذلك؟
Are you guys having an "LQ"?
هل لديكم مشكلة في جودة الفيديو؟
You're not even at L yet and you're already at Q.
أنت لم تصل حتى إلى L بعد ، وأنت بالفعل في Q.
What's "L"?
ما هو حرف "L"؟
Love.
حب.
What's "Q"?
ما هو حرف "Q"؟
Q?
سؤال؟
A booger!
مخاط!
Is it funny, huh?
أليس هذا مضحكاً؟
Whatever!
أيا كان!
Just go look for a place to stay already!
اذهب وابحث عن مكان للإقامة!
So you can finally leave!
إذن يمكنك المغادرة أخيراً!
It's quarrel.
إنه شجار.
Lovers' Quarrel.
شجار بين حبيبين.
You and Keifer.
أنت وكيفر.
We're not lovers.
لسنا عشاقاً.
Exactly. You're not even at L yet, already at Q.
بالضبط. أنت لم تصل حتى إلى L بعد، بل وصلت بالفعل إلى Q.
Moving fast, huh.
يتحركون بسرعة، أليس كذلك؟
I don't know.
لا أعرف.
I don't want to talk about it right now.
لا أريد التحدث عن ذلك الآن.
I almost died earlier, didn't I?
كدتُ أموت في وقت سابق، أليس كذلك؟
And he was being so mean!
وكان لئيماً للغاية!
I had a gun pointed at me and I didn't even get a thank you?
لقد وُجّه إليّ سلاح ولم أتلقَ حتى كلمة شكر؟
So annoying.
مزعج للغاية.
Jay, Keifer asked me to tell you something.
جاي، طلب مني كيفر أن أخبرك بشيء.
What?
ماذا؟
If you don't show up in 5 minutes,
إذا لم تحضر خلال 5 دقائق،
he said he'll talk to Angelo.
قال إنه سيتحدث مع أنجيلو.
What?
ماذا؟
He'll show up and talk? What does that mean?
هل سيحضر ويتحدث؟ ماذا يعني ذلك؟
Jay, he's downstairs.
جاي، إنه في الطابق السفلي.
- Downstairs?! - Downstairs!
- في الطابق السفلي؟! - في الطابق السفلي!
- Hurry! - Wait!
- أسرع! - انتظر!
Give me your Yogorino.
أعطني يوغورينو الخاص بك.
- I'll eat that later! - Go!
سآكل ذلك لاحقاً! - هيا!
Jay.
جاي.
I know you're mad, so…
أعلم أنك غاضب، لذا...
please say something.
أرجوك قل شيئاً.
So just because I'm mad, I have to speak first?
هل يعني هذا أنني مضطر للتحدث أولاً لمجرد أنني غاضب ؟
Is this about what I said earlier?
هل هذا يتعلق بما قلته سابقاً؟
And that's coming from the person who is the reason why I'm mad in the first place!
وهذا الكلام صادر من الشخص الذي هو السبب في غضبي من الأساس!
At least you're aware!
على الأقل أنت على دراية!
Now, you talk first.
والآن، تكلم أنت أولاً.
Why me?
لماذا أنا؟
What should I tell you?
ماذا عليّ أن أخبرك؟
Tsss.
ششش.
Apologize!
يعتذر!
Jay, look.
جاي، انظر.
I know I hurt your feelings,
أعلم أنني جرحت مشاعرك،
but what you did earlier was wrong.
لكن ما فعلته سابقاً كان خطأً.
What if Dylan has done something?
ماذا لو فعل ديلان شيئاً ما؟
Did he? No, right?
هل فعل ذلك؟ لا، صحيح؟
Still wrong!
ما زلت مخطئاً!
So what?
وماذا في ذلك؟
That's my point!
هذا ما أقصده!
I already put my life on the line!
لقد خاطرت بحياتي بالفعل!
And I don't even get a bit of credit?
ولا أحصل حتى على ذرة من التقدير؟
Damn it.
عليك اللعنة.
I should've just let you sign that damn paper.
كان عليّ أن أدعك توقع على تلك الورقة اللعينة.
What?!
ماذا؟!
Three.
ثلاثة.
What do you mean "three"?
ماذا تقصد بكلمة "ثلاثة"؟
That was three words.
كانت تلك ثلاث كلمات.
Profanity.
ألفاظ نابية.
- No! - We had a deal.
- لا! - لقد اتفقنا.
I know we had a deal,
أعلم أننا اتفقنا،
but since I'm mad,
لكن بما أنني غاضب،
kiss your own face!
قبّل وجهك!
Fine, you win.
حسناً، لقد فزت.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Thank you,
شكرًا لك،
for risking you life to save me and my brothers.
لأنك خاطرت بحياتك لإنقاذي أنا وإخوتي.
You worried me to death.
لقد أقلقني ذلك بشدة.
Whatever!
أيا كان!
I'm still mad.
ما زلت غاضباً.
Huh? Why?
هاه؟ لماذا؟
Because I feel like
لأنني أشعر بـ
I don't really know you that well.
أنا لا أعرفك جيداً.
What do you mean?
ماذا تقصد؟
What happened between you and your dad.
ما الذي حدث بينك وبين والدك؟
Okay fine, if you don't want to.
حسناً، لا بأس، إذا كنت لا تريد ذلك.
Fuck!
اللعنة!
Traumatic would be an understatement to describe my childhood
إن وصف طفولتي بأنها مؤلمة سيكون بخساً لحقها
with the monster who happens to be my father.
مع الوحش الذي يصادف أنه والدي.
Keifer, you lost to that Hanamitchi kid again.
كيفر، لقد خسرت أمام ذلك الطفل هاناميتشي مرة أخرى.
When you show them that you're losing,
عندما تُظهر لهم أنك تخسر،
they'll push you down even more.
سوف يدفعونك إلى الأسفل أكثر.
They'll use you.
سيستغلونك.
They'll break you.
سوف يحطمونك.
Mark Keifer Watson!
مارك كيفر واتسون!
To the Guidance Office!
إلى مكتب الإرشاد!
That's why the first time I won against Yuri
لهذا السبب فزت على يوري في المرة الأولى
and we were taken to the guidance office, I was happy
ثم اصطحبونا إلى مكتب الإرشاد، وكنت سعيدًا.
because deep inside, I thought my father would be proud of me.
لأنني كنت أعتقد في أعماقي أن والدي سيكون فخوراً بي.
Why did you do that?
لماذا فعلت ذلك؟
Whatever it was, I apologize.
مهما كان الأمر، فأنا أعتذر.
If it really was my fault.
إذا كان ذلك خطأي حقاً.
I'm sorry Keifer, for what I've done.
أنا آسف يا كيفر، على ما فعلته.
That was also the first time I met Angelo.
كانت تلك أيضاً المرة الأولى التي التقيت فيها بأنجيلو.
Angelo is as terrifying as my father,
أنجيلو مرعب مثل والدي،
- but that's where the comparison ends. - You're brave, starting a fight like that.
لكن عند هذا الحد ينتهي وجه الشبه. أنت شجاع، إذ بدأت شجاراً كهذا.
- Ouch! - What?!
- آخ! - ماذا؟!
He taught me to be strong
لقد علمني أن أكون قوياً
and use that power to protect others.
واستخدم تلك القوة لحماية الآخرين.
Especially my loved ones.
وخاصة أحبائي.
Serina! Where the hell are you?!
سيرينا! أين أنتِ بحق الجحيم؟!
Stay here for now, okay?
ابقَ هنا في الوقت الحالي، حسناً؟
What is this?
ما هذا؟
That man had been hurting my mom since I was young.
كان ذلك الرجل يؤذي أمي منذ صغري.
You're stealing from me, huh?
أنت تسرق مني، أليس كذلك؟
He was always just about the money.
كان كل ما يهمه هو المال.
He'd accuse her of stealing from him.
كان سيتهمها بالسرقة منه.
And then he'd hurt her.
ثم كان يؤذيها.
He'd hurt us.
لقد آذانا.
Kaizer, the kids are here.
يا كايزر، الأطفال هنا.
Not here.
ليس هنا.
Even you?
حتى أنت؟
When you were a kid?
عندما كنت طفلاً؟
Yeah.
نعم.
Damn, you dad did that?
اللعنة، هل فعل والدك ذلك؟
He hurt you too?
هل آذاك أنت أيضاً؟
My mom promised we'd leave soon.
وعدتني أمي بأننا سنغادر قريباً.
You really should leave.
يجب عليك المغادرة حقاً.
It's not good to stay in a house with an abusive father.
ليس من الجيد البقاء في منزل مع أب مسيء.
Angelo, teach me how to be strong.
أنجيلو، علمني كيف أكون قوياً.
I want to fight for my mom.
أريد أن أدافع عن أمي.
After three years, my mom, Keigan, and I finally moved out.
بعد ثلاث سنوات، انتقلت أنا وأمي وكيجان أخيرًا من المنزل.
For a moment, I thought we were free.
للحظة، ظننت أننا أحرار.
On the same year, we welcomed a new member of our family,
وفي العام نفسه، استقبلنا فرداً جديداً في عائلتنا،
Keiren.
كيرين.
Unfortunately,
للأسف،
It also made my mom forgive my father,
كما جعل ذلك أمي تسامح أبي،
welcoming him back into our life.
نرحب بعودته إلى حياتنا.
I braved a few more years after Dad came back.
لقد تحملت الأمر لبضع سنوات أخرى بعد عودة أبي.
But after Keiren was born,
لكن بعد ولادة كيرين،
everything went back to how it was before.
عاد كل شيء إلى ما كان عليه من قبل.
It even got worse.
بل إن الأمر ازداد سوءاً.
Keiren was 4,
كان كيرين في الرابعة من عمره،
when my worst nightmare happened.
عندما حدث أسوأ كابوس لي.
You're such a meddler!
يا لك من متطفل!
It’s my father.
إنه والدي.
I allowed that monster to do this to my mom.
سمحتُ لذلك الوحش أن يفعل هذا بأمي.
That was inherited by your eldest child!
لقد ورثها طفلك الأكبر!
I will never let him  take my siblings.
لن أسمح له أبداً بأخذ إخوتي.
Over my dead body.
لن يحدث ذلك إلا على جثتي.
You're so greedy!
أنت جشع للغاية!
What did you say?
ماذا قلت؟
You're so fucking gree-
أنت طماع للغاية-
Enough!
كافٍ!
You're interfering again?!
أنت تتدخل مرة أخرى؟!
Why?
لماذا؟
What are you showing off for? You're just my child!
لماذا تتباهى؟ أنت مجرد طفلي!
Do you understand?!
هل تفهم؟!
You think you'll get the inheritance?
أتظن أنك ستحصل على الميراث؟
Stupid, I'll die first before you get all of that!
يا غبي، سأموت قبل أن تحصل على كل هذا!
Do you understand?!
هل تفهم؟!
You go ahead!
انطلق!
I’ll handle things here.
سأتولى الأمور هنا.
- Mom, please. I won't leave you. - Please, go.
- أمي، أرجوكِ. لن أترككِ. - أرجوك، اذهب.
- I won't leave you.
- لن أتركك.
It’s okay.
لا بأس.
My dad killed my mom.
أبي قتل أمي.
It was all him.
كان هو السبب كله.
Mom!
أم!
Answer me please.
أجبني من فضلك.
Mom.
أم.
But, I failed to protect my mom.
لكنني فشلت في حماية أمي.
And I can't let that happen.
ولا يمكنني السماح بحدوث ذلك.
But now,
لكن الآن،
I will do more.
سأفعل المزيد.
I will never let him take my siblings.
لن أسمح له أبداً بأخذ إخوتي.
You already know he kidnapped Keigan before.
أنت تعلم بالفعل أنه اختطف كيغان من قبل.
And I still don't know what really happened to him.
وما زلت لا أعرف ما حدث له حقاً.
And even after all that,
وحتى بعد كل ذلك،
he was never the same.
لم يعد كما كان.
It's all my fault.
كل هذا خطأي.
And now, he wants Keiren?
والآن، يريد كيرين؟
I can't let that happen.
لا يمكنني السماح بحدوث ذلك.
Do you understand?
هل تفهم؟
Hey.
يا.
No.
لا.
Sorry.
آسف.
No, Jay.
لا يا جاي.
I just can't help it.
لا أستطيع منع نفسي من ذلك.
Your dad is horrible.
والدك فظيع.
I can't believe how much you went through, Keifer.
لا أصدق كم مررت به يا كيفر.
Jay, please stop crying.
جاي، من فضلك توقف عن البكاء.
Please?
لو سمحت؟
You're so brave.
أنت شجاع جداً.
I thought…
ظننت...
I thought my life story was already bad.
كنت أظن أن قصة حياتي سيئة بالفعل.
Turns out yours is worse.
اتضح أن حالتك أسوأ.
How did you get Keigan back?
كيف استعدت كيغان؟
I didn't.
لم أكن.
After a few years,
بعد بضع سنوات،
he came back.
لقد عاد.
With his new wife.
مع زوجته الجديدة.
That's when I had enough.
عندها طفح الكيل.
And then, I forced him out.
ثم أجبرته على الخروج.
How?
كيف؟
You're the only child who kicked their own father out.
أنت الطفل الوحيد الذي طرد والده من المنزل.
It's getting late, we should go back.
لقد تأخر الوقت، يجب أن نعود.
But Jay…
لكن جاي...
don't ever do that again.
لا تفعل ذلك مرة أخرى أبداً.
I won't let that man touch the people I love.
لن أدع ذلك الرجل يمس الأشخاص الذين أحبهم.
Including you.
بما في ذلك أنت.
Maybe we could-
ربما نستطيع-
No.
لا.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Bye.
الوداع.
- Good night. - Good night. Take care.
تصبح على خير. تصبح على خير. اعتنِ بنفسك.
Bye.
الوداع.
What?
ماذا؟
What was that? Where have you been?
ما هذا؟ أين كنت؟
So you're not gonna say anything?
إذن لن تقول شيئاً؟
Jay, that's the second time.
جاي، هذه هي المرة الثانية.
I've seen the one before it.
لقد رأيتُ النسخة التي سبقتها.
Saw what?
ماذا رأيت؟
Jay.
جاي.
Jay-jay, seriously!
جاي جاي، بجدية!
Are you ever going to get it together?
هل ستتمكن من حل هذه المشكلة يوماً ما؟
I'm fine.
أنا بخير.
Are you even listening?
هل تستمعون أصلاً؟
What's going on between you and Keifer?
ما الذي يحدث بينك وبين كيفر؟
Make it clear then.
وضح الأمر إذن.
Are you really pushing me to my limit?
هل تدفعني حقاً إلى أقصى حدودي؟
No.
لا.
Answer the question unless you want me to tell Angelo.
أجب عن السؤال إلا إذا كنت تريدني أن أخبر أنجيلو.
I don't know.
لا أعرف.
We don't have a clear understanding of what we are. We just like each other.
ليس لدينا فهم واضح لما نحن عليه. نحن فقط نحب بعضنا البعض.
Like each other?
هل يعجب كل منهما بالآخر؟
You actually believed that?
هل صدقت ذلك حقاً؟
He's just fooling you.
إنه يخدعك فقط.
You know what, Jay.
أتعرف ماذا يا جاي؟
You're so stupid.
أنت غبي جداً.
We're cousins.
نحن أبناء عمومة.
He's obviously using you to get back at me.
من الواضح أنه يستخدمك للانتقام مني.
I don't believe you.
أنا لا أصدقك.
You don't believe me.
أنت لا تصدقني.
What did he tell you, "I love you, to infinity and beyond."?
ماذا قال لك، "أحبك إلى ما لا نهاية وما بعدها"؟
Huh?
هاه؟
That's-
هذا-
Those were the exact words he told you, am I right?
هذه هي الكلمات التي قالها لك بالضبط، أليس كذلك؟
I'm right, aren't I?
أنا على حق، أليس كذلك؟
So predictable.
متوقع جداً.
Cause those are the exact words,
لأن هذه هي الكلمات بالضبط،
that he told Ella.
أنه أخبر إيلا بذلك.
Hey!
يا!
You're too pretty, huh?
أنتِ جميلة جداً، أليس كذلك؟
You're engaged to Yuri, but you also have Keifer?
أنتِ مخطوبة ليوري، ولكن لديكِ أيضاً كيفر؟
What's bothering you?
ما الذي يزعجك؟
I want to…
أريد أن...
I don't want to deceive Yuri anymore.
لا أريد أن أخدع يوري بعد الآن.
I'm sorry, Yuri.
أنا آسف يا يوري.
Believe me, I really tried.
صدقني، لقد حاولت حقاً.
But I still choose Keifer.
لكنني ما زلت أختار كيفر.
Keifer…
كيفر…
We still have enough time, to figure out how to stop them.
لا يزال لدينا متسع من الوقت لمعرفة كيفية إيقافهم.
Ma'am!
سيدتي!
May I go out?
هل لي بالخروج؟
Ms. Mariano!
آنسة ماريانو!
Actually ma'am, it's Mrs. Watson.
في الحقيقة يا سيدتي، إنها السيدة واتسون.
Jasper Jean Mariano-Watson.
جاسبر جان ماريانو-واتسون.
Are you dating Keifer?
هل أنتِ على علاقة بكيفر؟
- No. - What about Yuri?
- لا. - ماذا عن يوري؟
Huh… I don't under-
همم... لا أفهم-
I hope you don't regret not choosing Yuri.
أتمنى ألا تندم على عدم اختيار يوري.
Jay, get dressed.
جاي، ارتدِ ملابسك.
We're going somewhere.
نحن ذاهبون إلى مكان ما.
I want your full attention.
أريد انتباهكم الكامل.
Only mine.
لي وحدي.
You're so funny.
أنت مضحك جداً.
You're so ugly!
أنت قبيح جداً!